Guide to the Clubs, Societies, and Organizations at Yale Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Yale clubs and organizations, 1834-1975; Accession 19ND-A-378
  - ALPHA SIGMA PHI
    - Invitation to initiation, 1857 June 19 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - SIGMA DELTA
    - Invitation to initiation, 1856 October 3 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- "Yalesbians" [student group] flyers, 1983; Accession 19ND-A-434
  - Flyers for the "Yalesbians" student group, 1983 (Box 1)
- "The Forest History Society and its History" (paper), circa 1989; Accession 1991-A-077
  - "The Forest History Society and its History" (paper), circa 1989 (Box 1)
- Delta Kappa Epsilon photograph album, 1868; Accession 2000-A-009
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon, photograph album of the members of Yale chapter, 1868 (Box 1)
- He Boule membership book and plaque of A. D. Dodge, circa 1903; Accession 2005-A-071
  - He Boule membership book and plaque of A. D. Dodge (1903), includes clippings and note cards, circa 1903 (Box 1–2)
- Communal journal created by the editorial board of the Yale Literary Magazine, 2002-2006; Accession 2011-A-066
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Allison Stielau, 2011.
  - Communal journal created by the editorial board of the Yale Literary Magazine, 2002-2006 (Box 1)
- Delta Psi certificate of appreciation, 1910; Accession 2015-A-027
  - Certificate presented by members of the Sigma Chapter of Delta Psi, now St. Anthony, to Charles Purdy Lindsley, PhB 1875 and MD 1878, for his interests in the Chapter., 1910 (Box 1)
- Records of the Oriental Club, 1913-2002; 1984-2002; Accession 2017-A-052
  Conditions Governing Access
  Permission to access records requires written permission from a governing member of the Oriental Club.
  - Constitution and protocols, 1913 and undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and memoranda, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Membership lists
    - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting minutes
    - 1972-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting schedules
    - 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Oriental Club of New Haven: 1913-1988" by Gary Beckman (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Schedules and announcements, 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Speakers list, 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Records of Alpha Delta Phi, Circa 1920s-1930s; Accession 2018-A-049
  The materials are open for research.
  - Landscaping directions for theater productions, Circa 1920s-1930s (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Cast photographs and playbills, Circa 1920s-1930s (Box 2, Folder 1-2)